A Guide to the Lucy Lee Lancaster Papers, 1915-1989
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Membership Organization Materials
  - Blacksburg Consumers Club
    - Accounts Ledger (Box-folder 34:64)
    - Audit, 1940 (Box-folder 34:65)
    - Audit Materials and Records, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 34:66-67)
    - Bank Statements and Checks, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 34:68)
    - Bank Statements, Checks, and Invoices, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 34:69)
    - Bibliographies (Box-folder 34:70)
    - Binding, 1931 (Box-folder 34:71)
    - Business Ledger and Checkbook (Box-folder 34:72)
    - By-Laws (Box-folder 34:73)
    - Checking Account Records (Box-folder 34:74)
    - Correspondence about Maple Syrup and Sugar Products (Box-folder 34:75)
    - Correspondence, 1938-1945 (Box-folder 34:76-77b)
    - Correspondence about Ordering Purchases (Box-folder 34:78)
    - Correspondence about Roanoke City Education Association Study (Box-folder 34:79)
    - Correspondence with Winnifred Fischer (Purchasing Agent) (Box-folder 34:80)
    - Correspondence with a Citrus Vendor (Box-folder 34:81)
    - Deposits and Sales (Box-folder 34:82)
    - Eastern Cooperatives, Inc. (Box-folder 34:83)
    - E.C.W. and Bills, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 34:84)
    - E.C.W. Invoices, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 34:85)
    - EF - Furtsch, Treasurer (Box-folder 34:86-88)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1937-1948 (Box-folder 34:89)
    - Financial Statements, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 34:90)
    - Financial Statements, 1943 (Box-folder 35:95)
    - Grocery Lists (Box-folder 34:91)
    - Newsletters and Correspondence, 1983, 1985 (Box-folder 35:92)
    - Incorporation Papers, 1947 (Box-folder 35:93)
    - Information Pamphlets (Box-folder 35:94)
    - Invoices, 1940-1944 (Box-folder 35:96-99)
    - Invoices and 1940 Co-op Act, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 35:100)
    - Invoices and Correspondence (Box-folder 35:101)
    - Invoices and Correspondence, Christiansburg Fuel and Supply, Inc. (Box-folder 35:102)
    - Ledger, 1941-1946 (Box-folder 35:103)
    - Letterhead (Box-folder 35:104)
    - Members and Mailing Lists, Membership (Box-folder 35:105-106)
    - Minutes, 1937-1943 (Box-folder 35:107)
    - Minutes, Correspondence to Members, Financial Statements, 1946-1950 (Box-folder 35:108-109)
    - Newsletters, July 3, 1942 - Feb. 26, 1943 (Box-folder 35:110)
    - Purchasing Committee (Box-folder 35:111)
    - Receipts "C" (Box-folder 35:112)
    - Receipts, Farm Bureau Co-op (Box-folder 35:113)
    - Records of Orders (Box-folder 35:114)
    - Statement of Operations, 1938-1945 (Box-folder 35:115)
    - Stock Certificates (Box-folder 35:115b)
    - Subscriptions and Agents Order Book (Box-folder 36:116-117)
    - Vendor's Invoices (Box-folder 36:118)
    - Votes For/Against Liquidation of Main Store (Box-folder 36:119)
    - Statement of Operations, Apr 1, 1948 - Sept. 30, 1948 (Box-folder 36:126)
    - Southeastern Cooperative League (Box-folder 36:127)
    - Printing Department Deposit Slips, Receipt Sheets, Bank Statements, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 36:128)
    - Correspondence, Receipts (Box-folder 36:129)
  - Blacksburg Consumers Cooperative, Inc.
    - General Information (Box-folder 36:120)
    - Bulletins, Meeting Minutes, Memos (Box-folder 36:121)
    - By-Laws (Box-folder 36:122)
    - Correspondence, Letters and Membership (Box-folder 36:123)
    - Minutes, Bulletins, Price Lists (Box-folder 36:124)
    - Price Lists and Inventory, Newspapers and Brochures (Box-folder 36:125)
  - Blacksburg Cooperative - Concert Association (Box-folder 36:130)
  - The Blacksburg High School Athletic Foundation (Box-folder 36:131)
  - Blacksburg Junior Woman's Club, Antique Show Sale Catalogue (Box-folder 36:132)
  - The Blacksburg Music Club
    - General Information (Box-folder 36:133-135)
    - Clippings and Notes (Box-folder 36:136)
    - Programs (Box-folder 36:137-138)
  - Blacksburg Presbyterian Church (Box-folder 36:139)
  - The Blacksburg Regional Art Association (Box-folder 36:140)
  - Blacksburg United Methodist Church (Box-folder 36:141)
  - Book Club (Box-folder 36:142)
  - Boy Scouts of America, Troop 56 (Box-folder 36:143)
  - Buy-Low Investment Club (Box-folder 36:144)
  - Citizens for the City of Blacksburg (Box-folder 36:145)
  - Citizens for Community Development (Box-folder 36:146)
  - Classification - General (Box-folder 36:147)
  - The Committee of Concerned Citizens of Blacksburg (Box-folder 36:148)
  - The Delta Kappa Gamma Society
    - Alpha Lambda Chapter (Box-folder 36:149-150)
    - Certificate (Box-folder 36:151)
    - International Meeting, Golden Anniversary, 1979 (Box-folder 36:152)
    - The Iota State Organization, Alpha Lambda Chapter (Box-folder 36:153)
    - Christmas Cards to Lucy Lee Lancaster, 1973 (Box-folder 36:154)
    - Meeting Notices, Membership Directories, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 36:155)
    - Clippings, Newsletters, Minutes (Box-folder 36:156)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 36:157)
    - Notebook of Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 36:158)
  - Department of Commerce Trade Lists (Box-folder 37:159)
  - The Department of Theater Arts (Box-folder 37:160)
  - Early American Society (Box-folder 37:161)
  - Faculty Women's Club (Box-folder 37:162)
  - Foreign Student Sponsorship (Box-folder 37:163)
  - Hokie Club (Box-folder 37:164)
  - Institute of American Genealogy (Box-folder 37:165)
  - The Luther Memorial Lutheran Church (Box-folder 37:166)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 37:167)
  - Montgomery County Bicentennial
    - Correspondence and Bulletins (Box-folder 37:168)
    - Name Tags and Plaque (Box-folder 37:169)
  - Montgomery County Democratic Party (Box-folder 37:170)
  - Montgomery County Planning (Box-folder 37:171)
  - Montgomery Floyd Friends of the Library (Box-folder 37:172)
  - National Council of Senior Citizens (Box-folder 37:173)
  - The National Travel Club (Box-folder 37:174)
  - The National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box-folder 37:175)
  - New River Historical Society (Box-folder 37:176)
  - Phi Kappa Phi
    - General Information (Box-folder 37:177-178)
    - Initiation Notice (Box-folder 37:179)
    - Journals (Box-folder 37:180)
  - Retired Senior Volunteer Program (RSVP) or New River - Community Action INC, Drama, The Long Way Home (Box-folder 37:181)
  - Richmond Area Committee for Public Schools (Box-folder 37:182)
  - The Southern Seminary Junior College (Box-folder 37:183)
  - The Southern States Patron, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 37:184)
  - Southwestern Virginia Genealogical Society (Box-folder 37:185)
  - Town of Blacksburg (Box-folder 37:186)
  - Travel Club (Box-folder 37:187)
  - United Nations Children's Fund (UNICEF) (Box-folder 37:188)
  - United Daughters of the Confederacy
    - By-Laws of the Dr. Harvey Black Chapter (Box-folder 37:189)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 37:190)
  - Virginia Council on Human Relations (Box-folder 37:191)
  - The Virginia Federation of Music Clubs (Box-folder 37:192)
  - Virginia Library Association, Includes Correspondence, 1930-1938 (Box-folder 37:193)
  - The Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box-folder 37:194)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (VPI) Alumni Association, Woman's Chapter
    - General Information (Box-folder 37:197)
    - Announcements, 1959, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 37:198)
    - Bills, etc., 1956-1961 (Box-folder 37:199)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 37:200)
    - Constitution, Revised, 1968 (Box-folder 37:201)
    - Correspondence
      - 1955 (Box-folder 37:202)
      - 1959 (Box-folder 37:203)
      - 1964 (Box-folder 37:204)
      - 1966 (Box-folder 37:205)
      - 1969-1971 (Box-folder 37:206-208)
    - Letters to Alumnae, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 37:209)
    - Minutes, 1955 (Box-folder 37:210)
    - Minutes from Annual Meetings
      - Second Annual Meeting, 1951 (Box-folder 37:211)
      - Third Annual Meeting, 1957 (Box-folder 37:212)
      - Fourth Annual Meeting, 1958 (Box-folder 37:213)
      - Fifth Annual Meeting, 1959 (Box-folder 37:214)
      - Sixth Annual Meeting, 1960 (Box-folder 37:215)
      - Annual Meetings, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 37:216-219, 38:220-221)
      - Minutes; Pre-Registration 1965; 1970 (Box-folder 38:222)
    - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 38:223-226)
    - Newsletters, 1954-1968 (Box-folder 38:227)
    - President's Report, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 38:228)
    - Scrapbook (Box-folder 38:229)
    - Women's Enrollment by Curriculum, 1921-1966 (Box-folder 38:230)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (VPI) Cosmopolitan Club (Box-folder 38:231)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (VPI) Omicron Delta Kappa
    - Announcements (Box-folder 38:232)
    - Correspondence
      - 1975-1976 (Box-folder 38:233-234)
      - 1979-1980 (Box-folder 38:235-236)
      - 1984 (Box-folder 38:237)
    - G. Burke Johnston Award, 1976 (Box-folder 38:238)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1976 (Box-folder 38:239)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (VPI) Singles Club, Announcements (Box-folder 38:240)
  - Virginia Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) (Box-folder 38:241)
  - The Voluntary Action Center (Box-folder 38:242)
  - Women in Education (Box-folder 38:243)
  - World Future Society (Box-folder 38:244)
  - Unprocessed membership files (Box 38)
  - Unprocessed membership files (Box 39)
- Travel Materials
  - Mexico and Cuba, 1937 (Box-folder 40:1)
  - Ireland, 1938 (Box-folder 40:2)
  - Ohio, River/Bus Trip, 1930 (Box-folder 40:3)
  - Guatemala, by Boat, 1940 (Box-folder 40:4)
  - Columbia and Venezuela, 1941 (Box-folder 40:5)
  - Mexico, 1942 (Box-folder 40:6)
  - Mexico, 1944 (Box-folder 40:7)
  - Peru and Bolivia - Correspondence, Bills, and Itineraries, 1946 (Box-folder 40:8-9)
  - Mexico, Guatemala, and Honduras, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 40:10)
  - Scotland and England - Notebooks, Pictures, Fliers, and Tickets, 1948 (Box-folder 40:11-12)
  - Western United States, 1948 (Box-folder 40:13)
  - Canadian Railroad, 1949 (Box-folder 40:14)
  - Mexico, 1950 (Box-folder 40:15)
  - Mexico, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 40:16)
  - Alaska, 1953 (Box-folder 40:17)
  - England, Fall 1953 (Box-folder 40:18)
  - Guatemala and El Salvador, 1954 (Box-folder 40:19)
  - Columbia, Peru, and Ecuador, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 40:20)
  - Mexico and British Honduras, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 40:21)
  - Spain, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 40:22)
  - South Africa and Rhodesia - Notebooks, Lists, Postcards, and Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 40:23-24)
  - Thailand and Cambodia - Textual Material, Notebooks, Pictures, and Maps, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 41:25-27)
  - Brazil, 1960 (Box-folder 41:28)
  - Egypt, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 41:29)
  - England, 1962 (Box-folder 41:30)
  - Italy, 1963 (Box-folder 41:31)
  - Japan - Correspondence, Postcards, and Notebook, 1964 (Box-folder 41:32-33)
  - Mexico and Guatemala, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 41:34)
  - Greece, 1966 (Box-folder 41:35)
  - Australia and New Zealand - Notebooks, Itineraries, Tickets, and Brochures, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 41:36-37)
  - Chile and Easter Island, 1968 (Box-folder 41:38)
  - Ceylon, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 41:39)
  - Indonesia, Singapore, and Hong Kong, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 41:40)
  - Burma, Malaysia, and Singapore, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 41:41, 42:42)
  - Antarctica, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 42:43-44)
  - Algeria, 1973-197 (Box-folder 42:45)
  - Galapagos, Ecuador, and Barbados, 1974 (Box-folder 42:46)
  - Spain and France, Cave Tour, 1975 (Box-folder 42:47)
  - Delta Queen, 1976 (Box-folder 42:48)
  - Russia, 1976 (Box-folder 42:49-50)
  - England and Scotland, 1977 (Box-folder 42:51)
  - England, 1978 (Box-folder 42:52)
  - Mexico, Mayan Ruins at Usumacinta, 1978 (Box-folder 42:53)
  - Mexico and Guatemala, Mar.-Apr. 1979 (Box-folder 42:54)
  - Mexico and Guatemala, May 1980 (Box-folder 42:55)
  - Philippines, Feb.-Mar. 1980 (Box-folder 42:56)
  - Peru and Bolivia, 1982 (Box-folder 42:57)
  - Usumacinta in Mexico, 1983 (Box-folder 42:58)
  - Costa Rica, Dec. 1983 - Jan. 1984 (Box-folder 42:59)
  - Germany, 1984 (Box-folder 42:60)
  - Itineraries and Lists (Box-folder 43:61)
  - Travel Correspondence (Box-folder 43:62-67)
  - Correspondence - Andres Escamilla, Mexico, 1957 (Box-folder 43:68)
  - Latin American Notes (Box-folder 43:69)
  - Foreign Bank Notes (Box-folder 43:70)
  - Lucy Lee Lancaster's Christmas Abroad (Box-folder 43:71)
  - Travel Slides (Box 44)